moveandstay.com 2003-12-09

# Moveandstay Privacy Policy

Moveandstay.com is strongly committed to protecting your right to privacy.

The information you provide when you visit moveandstay.com is used to enhance the service offered on the site.

You can be assured that any information you share with us will be treated confidentially and will not be disclosed to anyone outside of Moveandstay.

## Access by Children

When parents or guardians permit their children to use the internet and other electronic media, they also permit distribution of information.

We encourage parents and guardians to participate in and be aware of their children's use of the internet and other electronic media.

No information should be provided to Moveandstay, or any person or company, by children under the age of majority in their country, state and/or other community without the consent of the parent or guardian.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

## Credit Card Information

Payment information (credit card numbers and expiration dates) is treated confidentially and will not be shared with anyone outside of Moveandstay and the financial institutions used to process payments.

## How Your Information Is Gathered

Visitors to Moveandstay.com provide various kinds of information. Some visitors submit personal information through our information/reservations forms.

Other data such as pages visited, site trends, user movements, broad demographic information, inferred preferences, as well as aggregate site data, are collected through your browser's cookie technology and IP address.

## Links and Directory

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at Moveandstay are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Notification Of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

## Our Partners

Moveandstay.com requires its partners to ensure safeguards are in place to protect the privacy of the information we share. We carefully select these Partners to ensure your privacy and the value of their offers.

We require the same safeguards for the information received over the Internet as we do for customer information received by telephone and mail.

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our user's information.

When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our reservation form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry

## Secure Form: SSL

While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers () such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing.

## Contact Us

If you wish to contact us, go to our **Contact Information and Location page**
